A Guide to the Papers of Hugh Scott, 1978-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Hugh Scott 1978-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10200-x
This collection consists of 10 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This addition to the Hugh Scott Papers was a gift of the Hon. Hugh Scott, 1985 May 7.
Scope and Content Information
Papers include four letters, 1975-1978, from President Jimmy Carter to Scott thanking Scott for his support for the Panama Canal treaties and a letter of support favoring recognition of the People's Republic of China; and a letter, 1980, from President Rodrigo Carazo Odio of Costa Rica concerning the Panama Canal treaties.
There is also an article by Hugh Scott entitled "Memoirs of a 1920's Law Student," printed in the Northern Virginia Sun, 1984 October 5; and a letter, 1984 November 6, from Senate Majority Leader Howard H. Baker responding to Scott's statement concerning Baker.
Papers also include a commemorative invitation to President Ronald Reagan's 1985 inauguration and a cover sheet indicating that the public inauguration would be held on Monday, 21 January. The cover sheet originally was sent to Scott by Senator John Heinz, chairman of the National Republican Senatorial Committee and requested a financial contribution to help the committee's "early efforts to preserve our Republican Senate majority in 1986."
Contents List
- Jimmy Carter, White House, to Hugh Scott, in appreciation of his "efforts in supporting the Panama Canal treaties" 1978 May 1, ALS (electrostatic copy)
- Jimmy Carter, White House, to Hugh Scott, concerning "recognition of the People's Republic of China," w/envelope 1979 Jan 15, TLS
- Jimmy Carter, White House, to Hugh Scott, in appreciation of his "support of effective legislation to implement the Panama Canal treaties" 1979 Jun 22, TLS
- Jimmy [Carter], White House, to Hugh Scott, in appreciation of his "efforts on behalf of the Panama Canal Treaties implementing legislation" 1979 Sep 26, TLS
- Rodrigo Carazo Odio, President of the Republic of Costa Rica, concerning the Panama Canal treaties, in Spanish 1980 Jan 18, TLS
- "Memoirs of a 1920's Law Student....," The Northern Virginia Sun, by Hugh Scott 1984 Oct 5, Printed (electrostatic copy)
- Howard H. Baker, Jr., Senate Majority Leader, to Hugh Scott 1984 Nov 6, TLS
- Commemorative Invitation for the official Swearing-In Ceremony of the 50th American Presidential Inaugural 1985 Jan 20
- Invitation for the Inauguration of Ronald Wilson Reagan as President and George Herbert Walker Bush as Vice-President 1985 Jan 2
- John Heinz, chairman, National Republican Senatorial Committee, to Hugh Scott, enclosing an "Inaugural cover commemorative, honoring the 1985 Inaugural of President Ronald Wilson Reagan," and requesting a contribution. 1985 Jan 25, TLS (copy)